yesprep.org 2015-12-20

# Privacy Policy | YES Prep Public Schools

**YES Prep Public Schools Internet Privacy Policy**  
Effective March 21, 2011

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

• Our Commitment To Privacy  
• The Information We Collect  
• How We Use Information  
• Our Commitment To Data Security  
• Our Commitment To Children's Privacy  
• How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
• How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our  
online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected  
and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point  
where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the YES Prep Public Schools’ website.  
On some pages, you can make donations and/or sign up to receive periodic communication. The types of  
personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information, etc.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online  
and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this  
circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself on our website to communicate with you in the way you indicate, or to acknowledge donations. We never publish or share your personal information with outside parties. The only exception to this is the use of your first and last name in donor acknowledgement areas on our website or at one of our campuses. Your gift amount or other personal information will not be included in this recognition. If you choose to make your gift anonymous, your name will not appear in any acknowledgements or lists that we make public. We use the information you provide about someone else when requesting a card be sent to them only to  
only to fulfill that request. We do not share this information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with  
advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on  
our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways  
unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise  
prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we  
have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure  
the information we collect online. To further protect your personal information, we do not store any  
bank account information and we only have access to the last four digits of your credit card number once  
it processes through our Transfirst online payment system.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or  
maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our  
website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by  
contacting our office at 713-967-9000 to request it. We use this procedure to better safeguard your  
information.

​You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by notifying is in writing or  
over the phone. If you make changes over the phone, to protect your privacy and security, we will also  
take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 713-967-  
9000 or send us an email at [receptionist@yesprep.org](mailto:receptionist@yesprep.org).
